Front-end Developer

Niloofar Arazkhani

Address: Iran, Tehran | Phone: (+98)9127829193 | Email: arazkhanin@gmail.com

Profile: https://www.linkedin.com/in/niloofar-arazkhani-1581025b/ | WebSite |

SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS

Front-end developer who loves to build good front-end platforms so the rest of the team can present its work in the best way since I believe that a good front-end can show the whole product to the client. I am always learning and am always a student. Investigating new ways and tools to solve problems efficiently. Over **4 years** of experience maximizing the potential of teams in both large companies and startups.

SKILLS

+4 years experience : JavaScript | HTML | CSS | React | Redux | NodeJS

Others: Redux-thunk | Redux-saga | Redux toolkit | Mobx | TypeScript | Next.js | styled-components | Sass | css-modules | Storybook | Jest | Cypress | React-testing-library | Axios | Restful-APIs | Webpack | CI/CD | Linux | Git source control | Agile | Scrum | system design

WORK EXPERIENCE

April 2022 - PRESENT (5 mos)

Executive Committee Member, Persian Online Platform - *persia* 35

PersiaJS is a coding boot camp focused on web development in Persian.

- Lecturing the front end basics with an interactive approach using online platforms with more than **100** participants.
- Coaching students to find a job, with an 83% employment rate.

May 2022 - PRESENT (4mos)

Front-end Team Lead, Sharif University - DataDays

DataDays is a yearly Data challenge in first rank universities of Iran, with many sponsors.

- Leading a team of more than 10 junior front end developers
- Executing a new project for students to join a competition related to the data field, which has more than **1000** participants.
- Implementing a new landing page for the event which made the view 2 times better.

May 2022 - PRESENT(4mos)

Front-end Senior Developer - SnappExpress

SnapExpress is the leading online supermarket ordering company in Iran which is a venture of Rocket Internet Group.

- Improving the performance of the website by 43%.
- Enhancing company sales by 30% through the development of new features.
- Using Webengage to manage data and increase sales by around 5%.

Aug 2021 - May 2022(11mos)

Front-end Developer - DigiExpress

DigiExpress is the leading online delivery company in Iran which is a venture of Digikala.

- Refine delivery time by 24% by developing and enhancing a delivery application for a new way of delivering.
- Through the use of end-to-end testing by Cypress and unit testing by Jest, the company reduced the cost of the test by **20%**.
- Implementing an evaluation panel for our company with **50**+ users to evaluate their own works for promotion.

Aug 2018 - Aug 2021(3 yrs)

Front-end Developer - Snappfood

Snap Food is the leading online food ordering company in Iran which is a venture of Rocket Internet Group.

- applying new features for expanding the company services which lead to 50% profits for the company.
- maintaining and refactoring the old codes which improved the user experience by 32%.
- Contributing to an integrated design system (using storybook) for projects in the company, accelerating productivity by around 38%

Education

Sep 2020 - PRESENT

Sharif University, Tehran, Iran - *PhD (Computer Science)*

Sep 2020 - PRESENT

Amirkabir University, Tehran, Iran - Master (Computer Science)

Sep 2020 - PRESENT

Amirkabir University, Tehran, Iran - Bachelor (Computer Science)

Languages

• English: Advanced Level (IELTS 6.5)

• Persian: Native

• French: Intermediate (a2)